

DMITRIY KUZMIN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Software engineer with 2+ years of work experience. Developing solutions in various fields from telecommunications management and marketing to cutting-edge researches of blockchain technology. Constantly investing in education and learning new tools for making better products. Seeking for further gaining and sharing experience as a software developer.

Date of birth: November 16, 1995 **Citizenship:** Russian Federation

Residency: Montenegro Marital status: Single EU work permit: No

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Creative spirit
- Fast and curious learner
- Team player
- · Result-oriented

LANGUAGES

- English · B2
- Russian · Native

CONTACT





github.com/xotonic

m xotonic.dev

in linkedin.com/in/xotonic

Herceg-Novi, Montenegro

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain developer, Remote

LuxCore · September 2018 - present

Design, development and QA a fraud-resistant self-hosted peer-to-peer cryptocurrency exchange tightly integrated with Bitcoin blockchain, writing API documentation and wiki.

Technologies:

- C++: boost, autotools, SQLite, QT.
- **Blockchain**: Bitcoin Scripting, Solidity & Smart Contracts, Atomic Swaps.
- Python
- CI: Travis CI

Software engineer

Eltex · August 2016 - September 2018

Developing data-rich front-end for B2B clients with dozens of pages for monitoring and configuration network devices, dashboards for both engineers and marketers. Maintaining and developing constantly scaling components of an accounting system, optimizing databases, collecting and analyzing metrics.

Technologies:

- Java: Tomcat, SOAP, Spring, Vert.X, Hazelcast, Vaadin, JUnit.
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Python
- Telecommunications: RADIUS protocol, NETCONF protocol.
- Selenium (testing framework)
- CI: Jenkins, Docker, Vagrant

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Nobosibirsk State Technical University • Sep 2013 - Jul 2017 Thesis - Development of VCS for online PL constructor

Extracurricular activities:

- Additional course: "Linux system administration and kernel programming"
- Additional course: "Android app development."
- Administrating GitLab server for students projects.